[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rowan Atkinsons movie career started in 1983 with a supporting part in this James Bond movie.", "correct_answer": "Never Say Never Again", "incorrect_answers": ["The Spy Who Loved Me", "Diamonds Are Forever", "You Only Live Twice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This natural satellite, named after Neptunes son from the Greek Mythology, is the largest moon of the planet Neptune.", "correct_answer": "Triton", "incorrect_answers": ["Nereid", "Phoebe", "Proteus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Many countries held national referenda before joining the European Union. Which of the following nations showed the highest support for joining (92% in favour)?", "correct_answer": "Slovakia", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "Ireland", "Lithuania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I sent a foul demon back to hell battling him through a seemingly infinite fall and lived to tell about it. Who am I?", "correct_answer": "Gandalf", "incorrect_answers": ["Aragorn", "John Mcclane", "The Terminator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average lifespan of a mudpuppy?", "correct_answer": "11 years", "incorrect_answers": ["2 years", "5 years", "35 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Bonds Aston Martin has what device, used against hostile passengers, in the motion picture, Goldfinger?", "correct_answer": "Ejector seat", "incorrect_answers": ["Blinding flashlights", "Electric shock device", "Tape-recorded hypnotic voice playback"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do Ronald Reagan, King Henry VIII, Charles Lindbergh, Jerry Stiller, Mel Brooks, and William Shakespeare have in common?", "correct_answer": "Each was married to a woman named  Anne.", "incorrect_answers": ["Each can trace his genealogy to Germany.", "Each had a sibling named Jane.", "Each one was born in a  year ending in a 9."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cocktails ingredients are as follows: 1 1/4 oz. Southern Comfort, grapefruit juice, pineapple juice, soda. They are all mixed and shaken with ice.", "correct_answer": "Southern Sparkler", "incorrect_answers": ["Lobotomy", "Kir", "After Five"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 1985 horror movie based on the novella Cycle of the Werewolf by Stephen King.", "correct_answer": "Silver Bullet", "incorrect_answers": ["Silver Dagger", "Silver Crucifix", "Silver Knife"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of pigeons and doves exist?", "correct_answer": "300", "incorrect_answers": ["200", "375", "250"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These fruits of the Family Musaceae are a valuable source of Vitamin A, Vitamin C, and potassium and are highly recommended by doctors to patients, whose potassium levels are low.", "correct_answer": "Banana", "incorrect_answers": ["Pear", "Strawberry", "Apple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the fictional Star Wars planet Geonosis, Obi-Wan learns that Count Dooku and Nute Gunray have built a new droid army, and that Gunray has ordered the assassination of which one of these?", "correct_answer": "Padm\u00e9", "incorrect_answers": ["Senator Bail Organa", "Master Yoda", "The Jedi Council"]}]